Guide to the Paul R. Eberts papers, 1951-2005
Eberts, Paul R. papers [ca. 1951-2005
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Paul R. Eberts papers, 1951-2005
21-33-3664
Paul R.(Paul Roberts), Eberts 1932-
ca. 61 cubic feet
Correspondence, Manuscripts
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence, notes and lectures for courses taught by Prof. Eberts, projects including Mayors' Survey and CARDI (Community and Rural Development Institute), papers and other manuscripts.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Paul R. Eberts was on the faculty in the Rural Sociology Department (later Development Sociology).
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence, notes and lectures for courses taught by Prof. Eberts, projects including Mayors' Survey and CARDI (Community and Rural Development Institute), papers and other manuscripts.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Eberts, Paul R.1932-; Cornell University.Community and Rural Development Institute.; New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences.Dept. of Rural Sociology.; New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences.Dept. of Development Sociology.
Subjects:
Sociology, Rural--Study and teaching.; Rural development--Sociological aspects.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Closed for processing.
CONTAINER LIST
- Community Change and Development Extension, 1975-1979 (Box 1)
- Rural Sociology, 100 Course Outlines, Lecture Notes, Course Materials, 1966-1977 (Box 2)
- Proposals Project Data, Undergrad Course Notes (Personal University of Michigan), 1954-1970, 1951-1959 (Box 3)
- Undergrad Course Notes (Personal University of Michigan), Paul R. Eberts Papers, 1951-1959, 1964-1969 (Box 4)
- RPE Papers, Rural Sociology 601, Mayors Survey (Box 5)
- Mimeograph Papers RS 213 (Box 6)
- R.S. 641, 560, 602, CHRD Planning Council, Northeast Conference151, 1991, 1990 (Box 7)
- Northeast Conference151, Washington Meeting, Fiscal Austerity Proposal, 1988-1990, 1986-1987, 1983-1986 (Box 8)
- Eberts Papers, Canal Corridor, NYS Economic Development, Projects (Box 9)
- "00WB" Projects, Crosswords Surveys, Mayors Survey, PRE Papers (Box 10)
- CaRDI- Community and Rural Development Institute; Canal Committee, CDC- Community Development Committee, Projects, PRE trip (Box 11)
- CaRDI Production Files Reports-Growth in Mass. (Box 12)
- Paul R. Eberts, Northeast Conference 89, Northeast Conference 129- Rural Development Committee (Box 13)
- Courses- Rural Sociology 101, Rural Sociology 436, Rural Sociology 494, Rural Sociology 601 (Box 14)
- Courses- Rural Sociology 100, Rural Sociology 101, Rural Sociology 602, Subject Files (Box 15)
- Subject Files, Rural Sociology 213, Rural Sociology 100-Lecture Notes, Rural Sociology 101-Lecture Notes (Box 16)
- Courses- Rural Sociology 101, Rural Sociology 436 (Box 17)
- Paul R. Eberts, Courses- Rural Sociology 101 (Box 18)
- Courses- Rural Sociology 436, Rural Sociology 641 (Box 19)
- Courses- Rural Sociology 641, Rural Sociology 301,401, Rural Sociology 603 (Box 20)
- Rural Sociology 301, Northeast Conference 129, Northeast Conferece 89, Mayors' Report 1983 (Box 21)
- Northeast Conference 89 (Box 22)
- Subject Files, Terry Clark, Jay Foley, James Christenson, Regional Development (Box 23)
- Northeast Conference 151 (Box 24)
- Northeast Conference 151, Personal Papers, Agricultural Leadership, NYS Programs (Box 25)
- Course Notes- Rural Sociology 322, Rural Sociology 432-433, Rural Sociology 632-633, Rural Sociology 128-343-441 (Box 26)
- Rural Sociology 343-441-443 (Box 27)
- Rural Sociology 200-301, Sociology 51, Sociology 60, Sociology 262, Public Opinion Council-Interviews (Box 28)
- Sociology 101, GEM Study, Agricultural Leadership Program (Box 29)
- Ag Leadership Program, Paul R. Eberts-Papers, Talks (Box 30)
- Local Budgets, Economic Development Materials (Box 31)
- Paul R. Eberts-Papers, Talks (Box 32)
- Agri. News Service, Association of American Colleges, Rural Development, Economic Development Materials (Box 33)
- Courses-Rural Sociology 642, 632, 511, 624; Social Trends Outlook Conference (STOC) (Box 34)
- Employment Demand Data, Economic Opportunity Corporation, County Materials-Local Budgets, Watershed Management Materials, Water Resources Institute (WRI) New York State (Box 35)
- Legislative Commission on Rural Resources (LCRR), Materials on Aged, Community Development Corporation (CDC) (Box 36)
- County Reports-Data, Proposals, Reviews, Research Projects, Small Business Innovation Research (SBIR) (Box 37)
- Courses-Rural Sociology 642 (formerly 624), Rural Sociology 595-598, Belarus Materials (Russia) (Box 38)
- Department Extension Leader, County Reports-Data (Box 39)
- Research-Case Studies, Papers-Miscellaneous Topics (Box 40)
- County Data, Rural Public Administration, Miscellaneous Papers (Box 41)
- Community Power Structure, Recruitment Committees (Box 42)
- Project Proposals, Northeast Regional Conference 47-89 (Box 43)
- Northeast Regional Conference 74-89, Community and Rural Development Institute-Steering Committee, 1998-1994 (Box 44)
- Community and Rural Development Institute-County Data, Research Proposals (Box 45)
- Economic Development Conference, 1988-1990 (Box 46)
- Newspaper Articles, Northeast Regional and Center for Rural Development, Resident Civilian Labor Force Summary, Farm Worker Projects, NYS Project 2000 (Population), Community Resource Development, 1979, 1989-1998, 1989-2000, 1975-1998 (Box 47)
- Rural Development Data (Box 48)
- Rural Development Data, County Data, Sustainable Agriculture Data (Box 49)
- Sustainable Agriculture Data, Rural Sociology Course Material 331, In-Source Workshop on Interpreting Social Data (Box 50)
- Social Trends and Outlook Conference (STOC), 1985-1991 (Box 51)
- Social Trends and Outlook Conference, Correspondence, Meritorious Service Award, Cooperative Extension-Presentation by Epsilon Sigma Phi, Lambda Chapter, Cornell University, 1983-1985, 1964-2005, 1992 (Box 52)
- Miscellaneous Files, Newspaper Articles, Fort Drum Data, County Trends (Box 53)
- County Data, Adirondack North Country Association Conference, Massachusetts Data, Miscellaneous Papers, 1985 (Box 54)
- Miscellaneous Papers, Rural Sociology Department Meetings, Teaching Committee, Evaluation Committee, Department Committee Meetings, 1984-1990, 1988-1993, 1990-2004 (Box 55)
- CSRS Review, Rural Sociology Faculty Meetings, Field of Sociology-Issues, Economic Development, 1988-1989, 1980-1994 (Box 56)
- Economic Development Committee Reports, Rural Sociology 428-Local Economic Development, Economic Development Workshops, Regional Working Cabinets (Box 57)
- Southern Tier Economic Trends, Multicommunity Collaboration, Local Government Programs, Rural School Programs (Box 58)
- Community Land Use and Economic Simulation (CLUES), Community and Rural Development Institute (Box 59)
- Miscellaneous Materials, Cornell Research Center, Center Directions Meeting Minutes, University Lectures Committee (Box 60)
- Nanjing Delegation, Rural Sociology Issues, Adirondack Park Association (APA) Data (Box 61)